Adam Haviv

ashaviv27@gmail.com

L 050-818-1126

github.com/ashvv1

n linkedin.com/in/adam-haviv-84bb17225/

https://www.adamhaviv.com

Profile

More than two years of experience working on professional and personal projects. Fast learning and initiative-taking autodidact with English as a first language to the product from the ground up. Very processor to be applied to the product from the ground up. Very processor.

Has experience in planning, prototyping, and developing a product from the ground up. Very passionate about learning and creating. Looking for a Full Stack, Front End or Back End Developer position which will allow me to utilize my relevant experience as well as grow as a developer.

Technical Knowledge/Experience

- Databases: MongoDB, Firestore, mySQL
 Cloud: AWS (EC2), Firebase, Mongo Atlas
- Front-End: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript,
 Web3: Solidity, Web3 Integrations
- React.js, Next.js, jQuery, Svelte Back-End: Node.JS, Express, PHP
- DevOps/Workflow: Docker, GitHub, Jira, Jenkins, EC2, ECR, Netlify, Heroku
- Testing: Jenkins, Mocha
 -

Professional Experience

Software Developer, Cambium LTD, April 2023 - Present

 Developing a wide variety of solutions for several projects ranging from custom websites, automation and internal management systems for companies.

*Was previously in charge of project coordination and development of the product of a foreign client.

Soft Skills: Flexibility, problem solving, teamwork, planning, time management, autonomous learning.

Technologies: Typescript, React, Svelte, PHP, HTML, SCSS, MUI, Zustand

FullStack Developer (Intern), Minerva XR, August 2022 - April 2023

 Planned, prototyped and implemented an LMS system for Unity based learning modules. Implemented front end body tracking solutions in protypes requested by customers in the medical field.

Soft Skills: Team work, prototyping, debugging, planning and implementation of LMS; managed AWS services (EC2, ECR)

and updated Docker images; produced true to Figma frontend for LMS, frequent code reviews; Maintained API
Technologies: Firestore/Firebase, React, is, Node, is

Python Insructor, Nitzanim Program, October 2022 - June 2023

Taught 10th graders Python, following a syllabus intended to prepare students for Army service in cyber units.
 Soft Skills: Relaying complicated concepts in a simplified manner to high schoolstudents while developing their coding and problem-solving skills.

Education

SV College, January 2022 - June 2022 FullStack Development Program

Fullstack Development Program

Focus on MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node)

CodeCademy, October 2021 - Janury 2022

Online FullStack Course

- · Certificate of completion (Front-End Development)
- · Certificate of completion (JavaScript)

Languages

Hebrew - Fluent
 English - Native